[{"answer": "I'm not going to hurt you", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "This is my apartment", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Where are we going to go", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " I know we have to go. I am not stupid", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You're home early", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "How was the conference", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Are you hungry", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Uh...yeah. I like sharmas", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Where are you from", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh. I was in that place two winters ago. It was just beautiful", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "But he didn't mean..", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Where are you taking him", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No. my friend told me not to tell her. He doesn't want to worry her", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No. He has had no trouble. He is a good person", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Seven years ago", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yeah. We did everything they told us to", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Where are you from", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Ah. I knew it. I am from that place. that place. I'm my friend. Why are you here", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " I am Palestinian from that place", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I am visiting my son", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Do you need anything else", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Good night", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend said hello", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I can't really tell. He wants me to leave. But I am not leaving", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend sent me the CD for", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I haven't either but I think I know every word", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well, I thought that...we might do something", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "OK", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What facility? Where", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "that place? Where they had the floods", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No. No he didn't know anything else", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " my friend, what would you do if you didn't teach", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I think that is exciting. Not to know", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yes. Did you find him", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Removed? To where", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "He...how can that be? Is there any way to contact him", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You don't think so? What kind of answer is that?", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "So do I. You look cool", "docId": "Visitor_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yes. You are very cool, my friend", "qsentId": 42}]